Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Good Morning, Church!
My name is Damian.
I'm from Benue State, Nigeria.
I'm an Uber driver.
He is my friend from Ghana.
This is my mum.
This is my auntie.
I'm here today to testify of the goodness of God in my life through the ministration of the new Morning Water.
On the fateful day, I woke up in the morning.
I went out for my daily job.
In the evening, I came home around midnight.
Upon getting to my street, I was tired.
So I could not reach my house.
I parked near my house for me to rest.
Before I knew it, unknown gunmen attacked me.
That is the only thing I know.
The next thing, I found myself somewhere - somewhere I didn't know.
The person I saw where I found myself was my late dad who died many years ago.
He now called me for me to come.
It took a first, second step to reach where he was.
Children of God, I saw the man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Mr Damian, Friend & Family
New Morning Water Testimony
He now called me to come back.
I now turned and followed him.
So when I was going with him, I turned to look at my father again.
I did not see him.
That was how I woke up and I found in the hospital.
I now saw my friend.
I asked him, "Where are we? Where am I? What are we doing here?
I'm just closing from work".
He then laughed and told me that I was attacked.
My name is Philip. I'm from Ghana.
The man beside me is my friend Damian.
He is an Uber driver, and that is the mum and auntie.
Actually, I'm a business man. Most of the time, I come here to Lagos to do importation.
Any time I come, I call him; he is the one that normally takes me around.
So this fateful day, I came on the 10th of August.
I was in the hotel room and received a phone call around 3 to 4 am in the morning
that my friend was dead and I was like, "How?"
The person who called indicated that my friend was dead.
They took him to the hospital.
So I rushed to the general hospital.
On getting there, I realised that he was in a pool of blood.
According to those who saw him at the beginning, he was attacked by armed robbers.
They beat him and thought he was dead.
They threw him into the dustbin and left him there.
It was the security man that was passing by who knew where he was
and they found him and took him to the hospital.
Immediately the doctor asked me whether I was a family member.
I said, "No, I'm a friend. But if there are any bills, I'm ready to pay for him".
The doctor said, "Ok, if that is the case, they could not do anything over there".
So we had to transfer him to Lagos University Teaching Hospital.
We took him there. On getting there, they rushed him to the emergency ward.
When the doctors came - there were many of them -
first of all, the ones who were going to operate the head.
He was in coma at that time.
He could not see anything, he could not breathe, nothing - he was dead.
Let me put it that way: He was dead.
They were going to operate the head, eyes and teeth.
They were going to look for three different specialists -
the dentist, the one for the head and the one for the eyes.
At that time, they told me that the bills would be at least 2.5 before they could take care of him.
Even if he comes back, he will not be a normal person again.
So I was like, "Oh. This one - how am I going to handle this?"
Then, I didn't know any of his family members and everything relied on me.
I could not go anywhere; I had to stay in the hospital with him.
I said, "Okay. I will take it upon myself.
Any bill, even if it takes me to sell everything I have, I'm ready to do it to take care of him".
Mr Philip & Friend
New Morning Water Testimony
The doctor gave me a list of things they are going to buy for the first operation.
They wanted to do the head first.
I remembered that I had the Morning Water which the man of God had given to me.
I had then already withdrawn the money; I was having the money in my bag.
But I said, "No, let me prolong them a bit and see what will happen
because through the Morning Water, I know God can do something".
Mr Philip & Friend
New Morning Water Testimony
So I decided to prolong the doctors.
When they asked me to bring the money or buy something, I told them I didn't have money.
It was on a Friday.
When they told me to bring the money for payment or buy the items they told me to buy,
I told them that I didn't have money - just to prolong them.
So through that, I was ministering the Morning Water on him.
I administered the Morning Water first on the head and the eyes after the three days.
Suddenly, he just woke up.
Shall we put our hands together for our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ!
You mean, your friend that was in coma -
when you started ministering the Morning Water on him, that was how he came back to life.
That was how he just came back.
And he came back with a word, saying, "This is sweet".
after I had ministered the Morning Water into the mouth.
He said, "This is sweet. Minister more; put more".
I put more; I kept on ministering...
Put your hands together for our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ!
Testimony Time
They even used him for a case study whereby all the students around came -
just to use him as a case study to teach the students.
I knew this man was condemned already for them to use him as a case study.
You are no longer a human being.
They said that on Monday morning, they were going to take him to the theatre.
I said, "Okay".
Early Monday morning when they came - the three of them, all the specialists -
when they came, the first one looked at the head
and he said, "Wow. We don't need any surgery again".
Testimony Time
Immediately, he took pen and paper and wrote, "We are discharging him on your part".
So the one for the eyes came and said, "Hm, your friend is healed.
The eyes will be clear by itself so we don't need to do anything again".
Mr Philip & Friend
New Morning Water Testimony
And he also discharged him on his side.
Remaining the dentist.
Initially, the dentist told me that they were going to use 16 screws -
both from here - down, and from here - down to hold the teeth.
And each one is 15,000 Naira.
And then they were going to use something called 'German anchor'.
I don't know - medical whatever.
Each one they were going to use - 10 of them - and each one is 8,000 Naira.
So the doctor looked at him - that was the dentist - after the other two had discharged him.
That one looked at him and said, "No, I won't need all the screws again.
All what I need to do is a simple and minor operation that will not cost much".
Wow. Put your hands together for our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ!
Ok, brother. Can I ask you a question?
Why do you think all these specialists were like -
they had already told you they were going to do the operation;
it would take months for him to recover -
why did they suddenly change and say, they were not doing it?
Because I continued ministering the Morning Water.
And he started healing, even without doing the operation.
Without doing the operation.
To God be glory. Put your hands together for our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ.
Later on, they took him - that is, the dentist took him to the theatre
just to fix the teeth with a 'German anchor'.
And he told me it was going to take six months for him to recover.
In these six months, he would not eat anything - only liquid.
He was in the hospital.
After he came back, I continued ministering the Morning Water.
Anything they said we should give him - medication and everything -
I ministered the Morning Water in it and I gave it to him through a straw
because then, he could not open the mouth.
Three days - I mean, three days - the doctor came back, checked him
and said, "This thing needs to be removed.
That the teeth are strong enough for him to chew bones".
Testimony Time
And that was when he was discharged.
Six months turned to six days.
Wow. Put your hands together for our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ!
From there, I got to know where the mother was
so I decided to send transportation for the mother and the sister to come and help him
because then, I could not do so many things.
That was when I sent the transportation to the family and they came down.
They are now in charge by taking care of him.
Ok, we can see a board beside our brother.
Can you tell us - what are the pictures on the board that we are looking at.
Mr Philip & Friend
New Morning Water Testimony
As you can see, this is when they picked him from the dustbin.
There was no car to take him in so they used a condemned bus that was around to pick him.
This one - he was gone already.
This was when we took him to the general hospital.
This one - he was dead and gone.
The doctors referred us as they could not do anything about it.
That we should go to LUTE (Lagos University Teaching Hospital).
And here is when he was still in coma in the theatre at LUTE.
You can see the eyes.
Both of the eyes were condemned.
And this was after the surgery.
Look at what they put in the mouth.
When they put this in your mouth, can you be a human being again?
This was what they put in the mouth.
It took three days to remove them.
And here is what they used to hit the head.
And you can imagine, you are just seeing this side.
But the head like this - down was cracked.
It cracked down.
So they wanted to fix the whole thing.
But through the ministration of the Morning Water, all this thing was healed within three days.
Put your hands together beautifully for our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ!
The same yesterday, today and forever!
Put your hands together for Jesus Christ!
Wow.
Indeed, our God is a miraculous God.
To God be the glory. Thank God Almighty for what the Lord has done in the life of our brother,
restoring him back to life; someone that could have been a dead person.
But through the medium of the New Morning Water, God Almighty restored him back to life.
There was something I forgot - whilst ministering the Morning Water.
There was a man - an elderly man - who was suffering from Parkinson.
He was shaking; you would see him shaking on the bed.
Immediately I ministered the Morning Water, the elderly man called me at my back and said,
"My son, please, is it the Morning Water from Prophet T.B. Joshua?"
I said, "Daddy, please, yes".
He said, "Can you minister it to me".
I handed the whole bottle to him, "Daddy, please take and minister it upon yourself".
And he did. The following day, they discharged him.
Testimony Time
Wow. To God be the glory.
So that means that the New Morning Water was not only for your brother.
It was also for everyone.
For everyone.
Wow. We thank God Almighty for what the Lord has done in your life and the life of our brother.
So now tell us, brother - what can you say concerning this New Morning Water?
The New Morning Water is the medium God has given us freely to heal, save and deliver.
Whatever problem you are suffering from, be it HIV, hypertension,
Hepatitis B, whatever being the case -
just use a drop of it and you will be whole.
You will be free, in Jesus' name.
When he was in the hospital, I remembered that I needed to go back to the police station
and report the case because then, there were no family members around.
On getting to the police station, I saw the car parked there.
So I asked, "How come?"
They said, "The same morning they recovered the car -
when the armed robbers were trying to use the car to rob somewhere,
they got them and recovered the car immediately that morning".
Wow. To God be the glory.
Put your hands together for our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ!
So not only did God heal him and restore him back to life,
his means of livelihood that could have been taken away from him,
God also brought it back to him.
Wow. We thank God Almighty for what the Lord has done in your lives.
My brothers and sisters, I was dead; I was gone.
I did not know what was happening.
But God brought me back to life through this Morning Water.
Mr Damian, Friend & Family
New Morning Water Testimony
My advice to the viewers, especially the taxi drivers:
Every time you are going out in the morning,
ask God, pray to God, tell Him to take over your life,
tell Him to lead you and bring you back safely
because without Jesus, I would not be alive today.
To my brothers and sisters, let us ask from God first, any time we are going out.
Thank you.
Thank you very much for that wonderful advice.
Our brother is telling us that we should involve God in everything that we do,
put God first in everything that you do
because the greatest decision you can make in life is to put God first in everything you do.
We also want to advise you, our brother,
as God has done this for you, make sure you make God's Word the standard for your life
and live your life in tune with God's Word
so it shall continue to be well with you, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
TT: Mel Flowers 05/02/2019
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 14/02/2019